young-america.com 2018-05-29

# Privacy Policy - YA

**Young America, LLC** is an engagement company that helps its clients market to their customers.  This Privacy Policy (“ **Policy** ”) applies to any website that is owned or controlled by YA and its affiliates or subsidiaries (collectively “ **YA** ”) and that posts a link to this Policy (“ **Sites** ”). This Policy only covers information collected at the Sites and does not cover any information collected at any other website (including our clients’ websites) or offline by YA (unless specifically stated). This Policy describes our information collection and sharing practices, including the types of information we collect from visitors to the Sites and how we may use that information. By using the Sites, you consent to this Policy

**This Privacy Policy Explains:**

  * **Information Collection**
  * **Community Forums & User Content**
  * **Information Use**
  * **Analytics Providers**
  * **Tracking Technologies**
  * **How We Respond to “Do Not Track” Signals**
  * **Information Sharing**
  * **Social Media Features and Platform Integration**
  * **Links to other Websites**
  * **Security**
  * **Information Collection**
  * **Users Residing Outside of the United States and Consent to Transfer**
  * **Changes to this Privacy Policy**
  * **Contact Us**

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

We collect a variety of information from users as they visit the Sites. For example, you may provide us with information, including personal information (information that is linked to a specific, identifiable individual, such as email address, phone number, and first and last names )(“ **Personal Information** ”), demographic information (your age, gender, ZIP code or similar information, business information (including your employer, and business contact information).  If we associate non-personal information with Personal Information we will treat the combined information as Personal Information. We mainly use Personal Information to communicate with you, such as through our email newsletters, to reply to a question, or to respond to your employment application. You may choose to remove yourself from our newsletter and promotional email mailing list (i.e., opt out), by following the link provided in the email received.

In addition, our Sites may automatically or passively collect information as you access and use the Sites, such as IP address and browser or device identifier (“ **Usage Information** ”), primarily for analytics purposes. The Usage Information we collect is generally non-identifying, but if we associate it with you as a specific and identifiable person, we will treat it as Personal Information. We may also receive information about you from third parties and we may supplement the information we collect with outside records. We may combine the information we receive from those other sources with information we collect through the Sites. In those cases, we will apply this Policy to the combined information. The Sites are for a general audience and we do not knowingly collect information from those younger than 13 years old.

**COMMUNITY FORUMS & USER CONTENT **

The Sites may provide you the opportunity to participate and post content publicly in forums, through interactive features and through other communication functionality, including through a “comment” or “contact us” feature (“ **Community Forums** “).  You may choose, through such features or otherwise, to submit or post questions, comments, suggestions or other content, (collectively, “ **User** **Content** “).  Please note that certain information, such as your name, may be publicly displayed on the Sites along with your User Content.

**INFORMATION USE**

We may use the information collected from visitors to the Sites:

  * to enable you to use our Sites and to participate in features we offer;
  * to communicate with you, including through email newsletters, to respond to users who have contacted us, to contact you with administrative communications and, in our discretion, changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use or any of our other policies;
  * to understand how visitors use the Sites, to improve our Sites, products, and services and for other internal business purposes;
  * to process information you provide via our Sites, including verifying that your email address is active and valid;
  * to assess your employment application and prepare related governmental and internal statistics reports;
  * to comply with regulatory and legal obligations; and
  * for purposes as disclosed at the time you provide your information, with your consent, and as further described in this Policy.

**ANALYTICS PROVIDERS**

We may use analytics providers to help us understand and analyze the types of users who visit the Sites and how they use the Sites. In order to provide their services, these analytics providers collect information from and about you, including Usage Information and may set and access their own tracking technologies on your device (including cookies and web beacons).

**TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

We, and our vendors and analytics providers, may use tracking technologies, such as cookies web beacons, and embedded scripts. We may use tracking technologies for a variety of purposes, including to help us gather information for analytics purposes, to let us know who opened our newsletters, and for fraud detection.

“Cookies” are pieces of information (data files) transferred to a browser when the user visits a site. Cookies store a unique identifier for a device through the web browser used. We may use cookies for various purposes, including remembering information that will make your use of the Sites more convenient and to track the total number of visitors to our Sites on an aggregate basis. You can find more information about cookies and how they work at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “pixel tags,” “1×1 GIFs,” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our web pages and email messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or email can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, to count visitors to the Sites, to monitor how users navigate the Sites, to count how many emails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular links were actually viewed.

An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device from our web server or that of a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

**HOW WE RESPOND TO “DO NOT TRACK” SIGNALS**

Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, the Sites do not alter its practices when it receives a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/). 

**INFORMATION SHARING**

We may share non-personal information, such as Usage Information and aggregated user statistics, with third parties in our discretion. We do not share personal information with third parties for those third parties’ own marketing purposes. We may share your information, including Personal Information, with our clients with your consent, as disclosed at the time we collect the information, as otherwise described in this Policy, and under the following circumstances:

  * with our vendors or service providers, such as a web hosting company, analytics service providers, or an email newsletter service in order to provide services to us or to you **;**
  * to comply with legal process or a subpoena or to otherwise comply with law or regulation, or at the request of a governmental entity conducting an investigation;
  * to protect and defend the legal rights or property of YA, our Sites or their users, or any other party, and to protect the health and safety of our users or the general public; and
  * with its parent and affiliates, primarily for business and operational purposes.  In the event YA goes through a business transition (such as a merger, acquisition by another company, bankruptcy, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process), your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. By providing your Personal Information, you agree that we may transfer such information to the acquiring entity without your further consent.

In addition, if you apply for a job through the Sites, YA may ask you to provide self-identifying information (such as veteran status, gender and ethnicity) in conjunction with laws and regulations enforced by the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (“ **EEOC** ”) and other federal, state and local regulatory agencies. Providing such self-identifying information is voluntary, but if you do provide such information, YA or its service provider may submit that information to the appropriate government or regulatory agencies to fulfill reporting requirements and use that information to defend against employment-related complaints.

**SOCIAL-MEDIA FEATURES AND PLATFORM INTEGRATION**

The Sites may permit interactions with a third-party website or service or contain integration with third party platforms. For example, we may use a website tool to display videos and we may contract with a third party platform to display content, such as tweets or other online posts. The Sites may also enabling you to “share” or “tweet” Site content to other online services. If you choose to “share” or “tweet” content (or to otherwise post information from or via the Sites) to a third-party website or other online service, that information may be publicly displayed and the third-party website may have access to information about you and your use of our Sites.  Similarly, if you interact with YA through a third-party service, we may have access to information about you (for example, if you “like” or “follow” us through a third-party service or if other users of a third-party service give us access to their profiles and you are one of their “connections”). The information we collect in connection with such social-media features and platform integration is subject to this Policy. Your interactions with third parties through these types of social-media features are governed by the privacy practices of those third parties, including your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party service

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

The Sites may contain links to third-party websites, such as our pages available through Facebook, Twitter and other third party social media platforms. YA takes no responsibility for the content, operation or privacy practices of third party websites and platforms.

**SECURITY**

We use commercially reasonable security measures to help secure your Personal Information. However, no system can be guaranteed 100% secure. We therefore cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, or that we transmit to you, or guarantee that it will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. You use the Sites and provide us with information at your own initiative and risk.

**USERS RESIDING OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES AND CONSENT TO TRANSFER    
**The Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located in another jurisdiction, please be aware that information you provide to us will be transferred to and processed in the United States and other jurisdictions. By using the Sites or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer, processing, and storage of your information in the United States and other jurisdictions, where the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside or are a citizen.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to change or modify this Policy in our discretion at any time and will notify you of material changes by posting the changed or modified Privacy Policy on our Sites. We may also provide notice to you in other ways in our discretion, such as through contact information you have provided. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Policy unless otherwise specified and your continued use of the Sites after the effective date of the revised Policy (or such other act as specified in the revised Policy) will constitute your consent to those changes. However, we will not, without your consent, use your Personal Information in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time your Personal Information was collected.

**CONTACT US**

If you would like more information about this Policy, or about YA’s online privacy practices please contact us: [legal@yaengage.com](mailto:legal@yaengage.com) or Privacy Team, Young America LLC, 10 South Fifth Street, 7th Floor, Minneapolis, MN  55402.
